setcom.com 2017-11-28

# Privacy - SID - South Africa's Most Secure Instant EFT Solution

This Policy was last modified on May 17th 2017.  
This Privacy Policy describes how SID Instant EFT collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: [www.sidpayment.com](http://www.sidpayment.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### Collection of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Financial Information such as bank or brokerage account numbers, types of investments
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

#### Use of Personal Information

  * The information collected from you is used to process your order.
  * The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to periodic company news, updates, and/or related product or service information, etc.

#### 3rd Party Disclosure

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

**Web Beacons**  
Our web pages contain electronic images known as Web Beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others who use our website. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of SID Instant EFT. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

#### Private Information Security

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, Setcom (Pty) Ltd, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We wil retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@sidpayment.com](mailto:support@sidpayment.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [support@sidpayment.com](mailto:support@sidpayment.com).

#### Additional Policy Information

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at support@sidpayment.com.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

**SID Instant EFT**

Monte Circle, 2nd Floor, Block A  
64 Montecasino Boulevard  
Fourways, 2191

**Email:** support@sidpayment.com  
**Phone:** +27 (0)11 555 1101
